(Howard:)Professor,
can you identify our cricket?
(Prof Crawley:)Of course I can.
(Prof Crawley:)I can identify every insect
and arachnid on the planet.
Not that that's gonna keep me from
having to move in with my daughter...
(Prof Crawley:)...in Oxnard. And we're not talking
Oxnard at the beach. No.
(Prof Crawley:)We're talking Oxnard
in the onion fields.
(Howard:)-Well, could you look at Toby?
-Toby?
(Prof Crawley:)What a stupid name for a cricket.
(Sheldon:)Told you.
(Prof Crawley:)It's a field cricket.
(Howard:)-Yes.
-No, wait.
(Sheldon:)Dr. Crawley, are you sure?
(Prof Crawley:)Young man, I've been studying insects
since I was 8 years old.
(Prof Crawley:)You know what they used to call me
in school?
(Prof Crawley:)Creepy Crawley.
(Sheldon:)Cruel as that may be,
that is not in itself a credential.
(Prof Crawley:)Let me show you something.
(Prof Crawley:)See that?
That's a Crawley's dung beetle.